{"data":[{"question":"Kent set out soon after dark ___ home half an hour later.","a":"to arrive","b":"arriving","c":"and arrived","d":"having arrived","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Simple past tense: We use the Simple Past to list a series of completed actions in the past.\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I'm sorry to keep you waiting. \"Oh, not at all. I  ___ here only a few minutes.\"","a":"had been","b":"have been","c":"will be","d":"was","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense:We use the Present Perfect to say that an action happened at an unspecified time before now\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Do you like the toy? \"No, it ___ very hard.\"","a":"felt","b":"is feeling","c":"is felt","d":"feels","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Simple present tense: the tense in this sentense must agree with tense in question sentence","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I don't really work here; I ___ until the new secretary arrives.","a":"have just helped out","b":"just help out","c":"will just help out","d":"am just helping out","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Present continous tense: Use the Present Continuous with Normal Verbs to express the idea that something is happening now","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"One more coin is need before my collection ___.","a":"completes","b":"has completed","c":"is completed","d":"has been completed","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Simple present tense+ passive voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"In some parts of the world, tea ___ with milk and sugar.","a":"is served","b":"is serving","c":"served","d":"serves","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple present tense+ passive voice: Use the Simple Present to express the idea that an action is repeated or usual. The action can be a habit, a hobby, a daily event, a scheduled event or something that often happens.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"How long ___ each other before they ___ married? \"For about five years.\"","a":"did George and Elizabeth know, were going to get","b":"have George and Elizabeth known, get","c":"had George and Elizabeth known, got","d":"do George and Elizabeth know, are going to get","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Past perfect tense + before simple past tense","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Alan's wallet ___ He has looked for it everywhere but still ___ it.","a":"is missing, doesn't find","b":"has lost, doesn't find","c":"is missing, hasn't found","d":"has lost, has found","answer":"3","explain":"\n- First blank: present continuous: implies the idea that this action lead to other action (looked) which is still in progress \n- Second blank: present perfect tense","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Claire's colleagues were all surprised when she made it clear that she ___ the office soon.","a":"would leave","b":"leaves","c":"had left","d":"left","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Future tense in past: would + infinitive","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Can Tony and I join your club, Dad? \"You can when you ___ a bit older.\"","a":"will get","b":"get","c":"will have got","d":"are getting","answer":"2","explain":"- Get older = be older","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}